{
    "subject": "resource/Ken_Fallin",
    "predicate": "ontology/training",
    "object": "resource/Parsons_The_New_School_for_Design",
    "human_readable": "Ken Fallin received training at Parsons The New School for Design.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.952399730682373,
            "question": "What might Ken Fallin do with the training received at Parsons?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8431994915008545,
            "question": "Where did Ken Fallin receive training?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7930948734283447,
            "question": "Is Ken Fallin a designer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7810290455818176,
            "question": "What institution provided training to Ken Fallin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7022596597671509,
            "question": "What type of design school is Parsons The New School for Design?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5815221667289734,
            "question": "Are there other institutions similar to Parsons The New School for Design?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5474469661712646,
            "question": "What field of study is related to Parsons The New School for Design?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5208678245544434,
            "question": "How does Parsons The New School for Design contribute to the world of design?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5128124356269836,
            "question": "Can you name any famous alumni of Parsons The New School for Design?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13339437544345856,
            "question": "What is the significance of design education?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ken Fallin received training at Parsons The New School for Design.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8355_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any famous alumni of Parsons The New School for Design?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8355_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does Parsons The New School for Design contribute to the world of design?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8355_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field of study is related to Parsons The New School for Design?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8355_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8355_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8355_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8355_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8355_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8355_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8355_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8355_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8355_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8355_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8355_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Ken Fallin studied drawing under the legendary cartoonist Mort Gerberg at the Parsons School of Design, which supports the statement that Ken Fallin received training at Parsons The New School for Design."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}